

Anh-Duy Tran

MSE in Computer Security and Forensics

Date of birth: December 4

Gender: Male

Phone: +84865202491

Email: pakkunandy@gmail.com

Address: 238 hamlet 2, Hau Thanh Dong Commune, Tan Thanh

District, Long An Province, Vietnam

Website: https://pakkunandy.github.io/

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research focuses include many subjects in Computer and System Security, mostly in Computer Forensics, Mobile System Security, Privacy and Software Security. I work to help organizations to inspect digital evidence in the cyber-crime investigation process, to design a secured system and software. My research style is interdisciplinary in general. I am leveraging many techniques and knowledge from many domains to tackle real-world security-related problems and design a secure system.

RESEARCH

My research interests include:

- Computer Forensics: OS forensics and Memory Forensics.
- Imaging Security and Forensics.
- Mobile System Security and Privacy.
- Software Security.
- Social Engineering.
- Applied Cryptography: Searchable Encryption
- Penetration Testing.
- IoT and Hardware Security.

EDUCATION

SEP 2017 - SEP 2019	EURECOM and Telecom Paris, France (Double Degree) M.Sc.Eng in Communication System Security Thesis grade: 20/20. Supervisor: Professor Davide Balzarotti
SEP 2016 - OCT 2018	John Von Neumann Institute - VNUHCM, Vietnam M.Sc in Data Science Working primarily in NLP and Regression
SEP 2012 - SEP 2016	University of Science - VNUHCM, Vietnam B.Sc in Software Engineering Thesis grade: 10/10. Supervisor: Professor Minh-Triet Tran

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2019 - Now VNUHCM - University of Science

Lecturer and Researcher in Computer Security

Researching Memory Forensics, Teaching in Software Engineering

MAR 2019 - SEP 2019

EURECOM, France

Supervisor: Prof. Davide Balzarotti. Final Grade: 20/20

JUL 2014 - AUG 2014

NEC Coprporation, Vietnam

Android Development Internship

CERTIFICATIONS

2016	Project Management, EURECOM
2015	Leadership Certification, JVN
2015	Summer Internship 2015 in NEC Vietnam Company
2013/2015	Merits of the Dean of Faculty of Information Technology for being in the Top 5 of Best Students in 2013 and 2015
2014	Participation second round Challenge Competition 2014

HONORS & AWARDS

2017 - 2019	Eiffel Excellent Schlarship for Engineering Student.
2016	Valedictorian (1/500) in Information Technology, FIT - VNU-HCMUS.
2016	Second Prize in National Competition for Innovation of Students XVIII - Euréka
2016	Gold Medal of "Designing - Manufacturing - Application" Contest – Ho Chi Minh City
2016	Special prize of "Master Key" Contest - Ho Chi Minh City
2016	Consolation prize of 25th Young Information Technology Contest – Ho Chi Minh City
2015	Sunflower Mission Engineering and Technology Scholarship

LANGUAGES

Mother tongue	Vietnamese
Other languages	English (Professional proficiency) French (Elementary)

UNIVERSITY SERVICES

⁻ Vice Chairman in The Associated Organ of Vietnamese Students' Association

⁻ Member of the Executive Committee in Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union of University of Science.- Member of the Standing Committee in Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union of the Faculty of Information Technology.

REFERENCES

Assoc. Prof. Minh-Triet TRAN

Vice President

University of Science, VNU-HCMC

Email: tmtriet@hcmus.edu.vn

Prof. Davide BALZAROTTI

Department Digital Security

EURECOM, 06410 Biot, France

Email: davide.balzarotti@eurecom.fr